pinstack.com 2012-11-21

# Smartphones: PinStack.com - Please read our privacy statement...

Updated: March 3rd, 2008 

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that PinStack.com. ("Service Provider," "we" or "our") treats the information you provide while using **www.PinStack.com** ("Website"). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. **Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy.** If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our [User Agreement](http://blackberryforums.pinstack.com/agreement.php). Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well. 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

**General**  
We collect personal information when you register, when you use our Website or the pages of some of our partners. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. Once you register and sign in to our service, you are not anonymous to us. We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser (cookies) for a seamless website experience.

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We do no rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if it is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before any private information about you is to be transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

If entered, your Blackberry PIN is published in various areas of our Website and by registering and using our website you hereby agree that we cannot be held liable for any reason whatsoever pertaining to any issues that may arise due to you publishing your PIN.

**Member Accounts**  
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to out service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and Newsletters, that are considered part of your Website account. We offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them within your profile options and Newsletters.

To delete your account, please send an e-mail or PM message to support@PinStack.com, subject: account deletion. Please include your full name, e-mail address in the body of the message. Note: By making this request you agree that we may ban your IP address(es) if we so choose. We do not provide refunds for Premium memberships. 

**@PinStack.com email account  
**The PinStack.com email service is a free service powered by Google's [Gmail](http://www.gmail.com/). We do not have access to emails or any communication therein. All email communications take place on Google's Gmail servers. However, we do own the domain name "PinStack.com" and thus we reserve the right to suspend or delete your account for any reason and without explanation. However, this is in an extremly rare case where we deem it in our best interest or in a discontinuation of this free service. Email accounts must be used for personal emails only. Using PinStack's email service for marketing, business or any other commercial use will result in a deletion of your email account and possibly a removal of your PinStack website account. In addition, you are also subject to Google's [Terms of use](http://www.google.com/a/help/intl/en/users/terms.html) agreement.

**Confidentiality and Security**   
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Your account Information is password-protected. In certain areas we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Third Party Advertising & Cookies**  
Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. However, we do not have any pop-up ads.

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. We may use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer.

**Kids & Parents  
**This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as follows:

**PinStack.com  
Box 362, St. Johns, Antigua  
Tel. (408) 480 0799**
